Guide to the Bayrd Still Papers MC.44
New York University Archives
- Series IV: Speeches, Reviews, Doctoral Student Files, Mayoral Research, NYU Archives, 1947-1976
  - Subseries A: Speeches, Reviews, Press
    - Milwaukee, Speeches on, August, 1948, 1948 Aug. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - NEW YORK CITY: STUDENTS' GUIDE TO LOCALIZED HISTORY: Reviews and Letters, 1964-1966 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Speeches, Miscellaneous, many as Acting Dean, University College, 1958-60, 1958-1960 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Remarks, "Dissertation: Training or Career," GAS Faculty meeting, Mar. 28, 1957, 1957 Mar. 28 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - "The History of the City in American Life," AMERICAN REVIEW, May, 1962, 1962 May (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Appointments to University Positions at New York University, 1955-1961 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Book Reviews and Evaluations, 1937, 1941, 1947, 1953-1980 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Letter to NEW YORK TIMES, Mar. 11, 1962, 1962 Mar. 11 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Urban History Group -- Correspondence, 1952, 1956-1968 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - URBAN HISTORY GROUP NEWSLETTER #1 (November, 1954) through #39 (April, 1975), lacking only April, 1969, 1954-1975 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225084 8
    - URBAN HISTORY GROUP NEWSLETTER, duplicates, 1954-1960, 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - URBAN HISTORY NEWSLETTER [British] #2 (May, 1964) through #10 (July, 1968), 1964-1968 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - URBAN HISTORY NEWSLETTER [British] #11 (December, 1968) through #15 (Spring, 1971), 1968-1971 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - URBAN HISTORY NEWSLETTER [British] #16 (Summer, 1971) through #22 (1976), 1971-1976 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Urban History Session at A.H.A., 1954 Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Dyos, H. J. Correspondence and Offprints, 1966-1970 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225085 5
    - Osgood, Ernest, "The City and the Frontier", 1947 Oct. 31 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Glaab-Smith manuscript, Critique of, 1964 Dec. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - "History and Urban Studies," Speech at Symposium at Louisiana State University, May 6, 1966, 1966 May 6 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies, circa 1964 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - "The American City Past and Present," Speech, Nov. 9, 1966, in University Scholars Lecture Series, "The Urban Dilemma", 1966 Nov. 9 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - "The Urban Dilemma" Essays for proposed book, not published because of editor's death. The authors: C. Abrams, B. Still, J. V. Lindsay, K. Clark, B. Rustin, F. Vigier, R. Theobald, A. Mayer., 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Callow, Alexander, Correspondence, 1966-1967, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Reaction to Milwaukee book, 1959 Mar. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Historians' Reactions to my 1941 article on Urbanization in Upper Middle West (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - McKelvey, Blake, comment on manuscript of, for Harvard University Press, 1955, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Charleston, S. C., Census of 1849, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Speech, "Living Landmarks," Sept. 29, 1964, 1964 Sept. 29 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Wagner, Robert F., "The City Takes a Giant Step," NEW YORK TIMES, Nov. 29, 1964, 1964 Nov. 1964 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Greenwich Village Historic District, Hearings, Dec. 9, 1965, Dec. 21, 1966, 1967, 1965-1967 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Subseries C: Mayoral Research
    Subseries C: Mayoral Research contains Still's research files on the history of the New York City Office of the Mayor, from the colonial period to the mid-twentieth century.
    - Mayors, 1665-1958 Cards for individual mayors, undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
      3 1142 04225089 7
    - Mayors, 1665-1958 Charts with biographical data, undated, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Mayors, Data sheets, A through F, undated (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Mayors, Data sheets, G through K, undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225097 0
    - Mayors, Data sheets, L through O, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Mayors, Data sheets, P through W, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Mayoralty, Footnoted chronology, 1665-1834 (ribbon copy), undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Mayoralty, Footnoted chronology, 1665-1834 (carbon), undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Residences of Mayors of New York, 1776-1932, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Mayors of New York Bibliography, to ca. mid-20th century, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - New York City Mayoralty -- Misc. Notes Rough draft, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Allen, Stephen (Seminar Paper of Judith E. Tobias), 1968 May (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Mayoral Politics Period of DeWitt Clinton, 1807, 1808, 1811, 1815 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Council, Members of, 1665-1776, 1869 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Mayors' Annual Messages, 1840-1860, 1845-1846, 1851, 1856, 1859 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Wilson, James Q., "The Mayors vs. the Cities" (1969) (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Subseries D: Archives, Talks, and Articles
    Subseries D: Archives, Talks, Articles includes more of Still's talks and articles, as well as files that document his work with the New York University Archives.
    - Advisory Committee on "History of New York University in the 20th Century;" Archives Advisory Council (1977-78, 1978-79), Oliva statements of Aug. 30, 1977 (Archives "Charter") and Nov. 2, 1977, 1977-1979 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225096 2
    - Adam, Emilie, undated, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Ackerman, Patricia, University Archivist, Jan. 14, 1980 - Dec. 31, 1980, 1980 Jan. 14 - 1980 Dec. 31 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Archives, Inventory of holdings, Jan. 30, 1979, 1979 Jan. 30 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Archives, Description of, 1970, 1977-1982 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Archives, Request for materials from University offices, 1963, 1969, 1971, 1980-1982 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Archives, Annual Report, June 1, 1979 to May 31, 1980, 1979 June 1-1980 May 31 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Archives Training Program; NEH Grant proposal; syllabi; flyers, 1974-1981 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Austern, Thomas, Memoir, 1979 July 25 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Bobst Library, Relationship of Relationship of Archives to, 1970, 1979, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Budget Material (not organized), 1967-1981 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - de Capriles, Miguel, Oral History Interview, Correspondence, undated, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Frusciano, Thomas J., University Archivist, undated, 1980-1983 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Gifts of Money to Archives by Margaret Brown and Kathy Goldsmith, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Graduate Assistants, 1980-1983 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Presidential Scholars in Archives, Summer, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Science, Inventory of records, undated, 1977, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Lutzker, Michael, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Sesquicentennial Exhibit, 1981-1982 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Munn Papers, Provenance, correspondence, etc., 1923, 1979, 1980, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225095 4
    - Munn Exhibit, Brochure, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Munn Exhibit, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Munn, J. B., Digests of annual reports as dean, WSC, 1928 Oct. 1, 1929 Oct. 1, 1930 Oct. 1, 1931 Oct. 1 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Oral History, Request for funds for, undated, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Picture Processing (Occhiogrosso), Request for funds for, 1980 Aug. 13, 1981 Jan. 20 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Town Hall Records, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Committee to suggest ways of memorializing the history of NYU and the people involved, 1922-1923, 1966, 1976, 1977, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Libraries, History of, Exhibit, 1964, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Stanford White Commemorative Stamp, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Law School Minutes, Access to, 1981 Jul. 10 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Hosay, Philip, Multinational Summer Institute, SEHNAP, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Literary Greenwich Village, Walking Tour, undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Dates of Ward Creation, NYC, 1791-1853, undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Gallaudet, Thomas H., Association with New York University, Question of, 1932, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Task Force Municipal Archives, 1961-1968, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Hudson Square, undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - New York City, Encyclopedia of, 1982-1984 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Falk, Minna, Memorial, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Spann, Edw. K., 1982-1983 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Sussex Tapes, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225094 7
    - Klotsche, J. M., 1984 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Clapp, James A., Program for Media & Urban Affairs, undated, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Luckingham, Bradford, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Lees, Andrew, undated, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, Plaque on 29 Washington Sq. West, undated, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Quinn, Terry, RASPUTIN, 1985 Jul. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Hansen, Bert, undated, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Chamberlain, Office of, 1969 Nov. 16 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Walking Tour, O.A.H. Meeting, 31514, 1985-1986 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Lecture, "Student Life at N.Y.U. 100 Years Ago," May 9, 1983, Class in Education E98.2069 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Brademas, John, Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - O.A.H. Meeting, April, 1982 -- Urban History, 1981-1982 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Script for taped interview and slide presentation on history of N.Y.U. at Washington Square, in connection with dedication of 9th floor, Main, Dec. 18, 1951, 1951 Dec. 18 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Lecture, "N.Y.U. Founding and Formative Years," Faculty Women's Club, Mar. 19, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Letter to Deborah Gardner on Teaching of Urban History, undated, 1947-1948 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Christopher Street, Naming of, undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - SUPER-POWERS, "Preface" (United Media International, Inc.), 1980 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Letter to Brooke Hindle, concerning S. F. B. Morse, 1981 Nov. 2 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Hermalyn, Gary, New York City History Project, 1981-1982 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Talk, "The Study of History in the Planning and Mid-Nineteenth Century Practice of N.Y.U.," Park History Honor Society, May 14, 1981, 1981 May 14 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Advisory Board of the Historical Records of the New York County Clerk, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - JOURNAL OF URBAN HISTORY, Editorial Board, 1979, 1981, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Adler, Susan, German Travel Literature, 1870-1885, 1973 Jan. (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Hood, Clifton, Thesis Prospectus, Columbia University, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Talk, "Greenwich Village -- the Suburban Phase, 1790-1850," N.Y.U. Forum on the History of Greenwich Village, May 10, 1979, 1979 May 10 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Talk, "Greenwich Village -- Suburban Days, 1790-1850," Washington Square Association, May 26, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - "Around the Square," sesquicentennial publication, 1981-1982 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Bernard, Richard M., Proposed updating of MILWAUKEE: THE HISTORY OF A CITY, 1977, 1981-1982 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Foreword for John P. Nielsen, PERSONAL GUIDE TO VILLAGE DINING, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 31)
- Series V: Correspondence, 1949-1985; 1962-1977
  Series V contains Still's correspondence regarding his work at NYU and research for the New York City Landmarks project. It also contains clippings, correspondence, and other materials related to Still's book Urban America and a Greenwich Village Walking Tour organized by Still.
  - Subseries A: Correspondence
    - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225093 9
    - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1951 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225092 1
    - Correspondence, January through June, 1970, 1970 Jan. - 1970 June (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, July through December, 1970, 1970 Jul. - 1970 Dec. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, January through March, 1971, 1971 Jan. - 1971 Mar. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, April through May, 1971, 1971 Apr. - 1971 May (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, June through December, 1971, 1971 June - 1971 Dec. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, January through June, 1973, 1973 Jan. - 1973 June (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, July through December, 1973, 1973 Jul. - 1973 Dec. (Box 51, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225091 3
    - Correspondence, January through June, 1974, 1974 Jan. - 1974 June (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, July through December, 1974, 1974 Jul. - 1974 Dec. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, January through June, 1975, 1975 Jan. - 1975 June (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, July through December, 1975, 1975 Jul. - 1975 Dec. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, January through June, 1977, 1977 Jan. - June 1977 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, July through December, 1977, 1977 Jul. - 1977 Dec. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: NYC Research
    - "New York University: A Sesquicentennial Overview", undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225090 5
    - Bayor, Ronald H. "Neighbors in Conflict: The Irish, Germans, Jews, and Italians of New York City, 1929-1941" AMERICAN HISTORICAL REVIEW (April 1979), 576, 1979 Apr. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Adrian, Chrales R. and Ernest S. Griffith. "A History of American City Government: The Formation of Traditions 1775-1870., 1976 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1981 through 1985, 1981-1985 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - "A Note on the History of New York University's Seal", 1981 June 9 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - "The Prince of Wales Visits New York University", undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - "The Founding of New York University, Pioneer in Urban Higher Education", undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - "The Founding and Growth of New York University" 9 New York University Data Processing: A Progress Review, undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - New York University Data Processing: A Progress Review, 1970 Oct. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Visuals for Milwaukee: The History of a City, undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Inventory of speeches, undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Invitation to "New York's Mayoralty: The Formative Years," a lecture by Bayrd Still, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Framed Photograph of Frederick L. Paxon, Noted Historian, undated (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - College, 1962, 1966, undated (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Letters to the Editor, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Lincoln Assassination, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Long Island House, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Lower Manhattan Plan, 1965-1966 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - MacDougal St., 1965 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Madison Square, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Maps, 1763, 1744, 1789 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Mayor, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Merchants House, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Metropolitan Opera, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Millay House, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Milwaukee, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Milwaukee, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Morgan House, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Mrs. Motley, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Municipal Art Society, 1962, undated (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Museum of the City of New York, undated (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Nassau County, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Negro, 1960, 1961 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - NYC - Architecture, 1963-1965 (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - NYC - Bibliography, undated (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - New York City - Current, 1961, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 36)
    - NYC - NY destroying self, 1963, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 37)
    - NYC - Early to 1800, undated (Box 52, Folder 38)
    - NYC - Historical, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 39)
    - NYC - Politics 19th and 20th C. (Garrett notes Party evolution), undated (Box 52, Folder 40)
    - O'Dwyer, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 41)
    - NYC - Econ. grow, 1959-1965 (Box 52, Folder 42)
    - NYC - Fire Dept, undated (Box 52, Folder 43)
    - New York City Historical, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 44)
    - NYC Literature, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225098 8
    - NYC - Metrop. Period Statistics, undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - NYC - Nationalities, 1962, 1965, undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - NYC - Museum Pamphlets, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - NYC - Water Supply, undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - NYU, 1966, undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Paramount Building, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Park Avenue, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Park Avenue, undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Park Avenue, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Park Ave., 1965 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Park Ave, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Parks + Squares, 1965, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Park Slope, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Patchin Pl. + Milligan Pl., 1965 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Penn Station, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Penn Station, 1962, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Penn Station, undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Philipse Manor, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Poe Cottage, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Police Dept, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Prospect Park, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Ramkin, Reb., 1965 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Rialto, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Roosevelt, F.D., 1965 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - St. George, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - St. Marks-in-the-Bouwerie, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - St. John's, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - St. Nicholas, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Savoy Plaza, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Savoy Plaza, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Savoy Plaza, undated (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Skyscraper Skeleton - Times Tower, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Alfred P. Sloan, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Stone, Edward, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Student Attitudes, 1964, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Subway, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Subway, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Subway, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Sullivan Gardens, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Sutton Place, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Surrogate, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - Tarrytown, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Travel Commentators, 1964, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Trinity Church, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - U. of Calif. Berkeley, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - U.S. Dept of Housing, Urban Devel., 1966 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Wagner, R., 1965 (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - Washington Hq, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - Wash. Square, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 50)
    - Water Supply, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 51)
    - Welfare Isl., 1965 (Box 53, Folder 52)
    - The West, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 53)
    - Whitman, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 54)
    - Williamsburg (Question of Restoration?), 1963 (Box 53, Folder 55)
    - Wilson House, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 56)
    - Wooden Bldg, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 57)
    - World's Fair Historic Docs, undated (Box 53, Folder 58)
    - World's Fair, 1964, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 59)
    - Wyckoff, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 60)
    - Wyckoff, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 61)
    - Wyckoff House, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 62)
    - York Avenue, undated (Box 53, Folder 63)
    - Yorkville - Cinema, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 64)
    - Ribbon Copy - (Master) AHA Greenwich Village Tour notes, undated (Box 53, Folder 65)
    - 1 - Boundaries of Greenwich Village: Map, undated (Box 53, Folder 66)
    - 2 - Greenwich Village - Aerial showing street formation, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 67)
    - 3 - Greenwich Village - Early Map & Street Pattern, 1822 (Box 53, Folder 68)
    - AHA Village Tour - Parade Ground, undated (Box 53, Folder 69)
    - AHA Village Tour - Montresor Plan, 1776 (Box 53, Folder 70)
    - 6 - Congestion on Broadway, undated (Box 53, Folder 71)
    - 7 - Colonnade Row [empty folder], undated (Box 53, Folder 72)
    - 8 - Leroy Place, undated (Box 53, Folder 73)
    - 9 - Washington Square North 1967 [empty folder], undated (Box 53, Folder 74)
    - G. Village Talk, 1974, undated (Box 53, Folder 75)
    - Illustrations, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 76)
    - Permissions File, 1970, undated (Box 53, Folder 77)
    - [untitled - more Permissions], 1970, undated (Box 53, Folder 78)
    - Permissions Inventory, 1973-1974, undated (Box 53, Folder 79)
    - Original - Permissions Listing, undated (Box 53, Folder 80)
    - Permissions Letter Forms, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225099 6
    - List of Excerpts with FEES, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Adams, J. - Belknap Press, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Adams, J.K. - The Rotarian, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Allen, Harper's Magazine, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Amer. Academy Polit & Soc Science, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - The American City - Buttenheim Pub, 1970-1972 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Bane: Nat'l Municipal League, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Baxter, W.T. House of Hancock, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Beard: Nat'l Municipal League, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Bello: Time, Inc., 1970 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Benson: Dover Publications, Inc., 1970 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Berger, Bennett, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Borun, Compiler: Nowiny Publishing, 1970-1972 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Boyle: The N.E. Historic Genealogical Society, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Breslin: Papert, Koenig, Lois Advertising Co., 1969-1973 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Bridenbough: U. of N. Carolina Press, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Business Week - Miami Nov. 1956, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Chicago Commission on Human Relations, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Citizens League, Twin Cities - Sub-Urbs in the City, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Douglass: Hawthorn Books, Inc., 1970 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Fisher, Sidney G. - Diary, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Fitch: Little Brown & Co., 1970-1972 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Foster: Pa Mag. Of History and Biography, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Franklin: U. of Calif. Press, 1970-1973 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Gans - Free Press, 1972-1973 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - George: Harper & Row Publishers, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Garrett - Lewis Pub. Co., 1972 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Gottman: The Twentieth Century Fund, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Greenwich Village Pictures, Notes, undated (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Grimsley: Reston Commonwealth, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Halberstam - Harper's Magazine, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Hallgren: The Nation, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Harrington, M. - Macmillan Co., 1972-1973 (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Hill: New York Times Co., 1970 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Hoffman, Hallock - The Center Magazine, 1972-1973 (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Hoover, Herbert - AmerCity, 1972-1973 (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Hoover & Vernon: Harvard U. Press, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - Jacobs: Random House, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - James: Little, Brown & Co., 1970 (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - Kotler - Bobbs-Merrill, 1972-1974 (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - LaGuardia - Columbia U. Press, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 42)